{
  "1": [
    {
      "_id": "1",
      "prompt": "Hello 1",
      "response": "Hi 1",
      "chatId": "6675ad0058154c87787cc4c4",
      "userId": "663a3f78970c6762815c0616')",
      "createdAt": "2024-07-01T17:36:21.254Z",
      "updatedAt": "2024-07-01T17:36:45.775Z"
    },
    {
      "_id": "2",
      "prompt": "Hello 2",
      "response": "Hi 2",
      "chatId": "6675ad0058154c87787cc4c4",
      "userId": "663a3f78970c6762815c0616')",
      "createdAt": "2024-07-01T15:33:55.287Z",
      "updatedAt": "2024-07-01T15:34:24.675Z"
    },
    {
      "_id": "3",
      "prompt": "Hello 3",
      "response": "Hi 3",
      "chatId": "6675ad0058154c87787cc4c4",
      "userId": "663a3f78970c6762815c0616')",
      "createdAt": "2024-07-01T15:29:17.131Z",
      "updatedAt": "2024-07-01T15:31:32.658Z"
    },
    {
      "_id": "4",
      "prompt": "Hello 4",
      "response": "Hi 4",
      "chatId": "6675ad0058154c87787cc4c4",
      "userId": "663a3f78970c6762815c0616')",
      "createdAt": "2024-07-01T15:02:20.822Z",
      "updatedAt": "2024-07-01T15:02:58.960Z"
    },
    {
      "_id": "5",
      "prompt": "Hello 5",
      "response": "Hi 5",
      "chatId": "6675ad0058154c87787cc4c4",
      "userId": "663a3f78970c6762815c0616')",
      "createdAt": "2024-07-01T15:00:44.595Z",
      "updatedAt": "2024-07-01T15:01:49.637Z"
    }
  ],
  "2": [
    {
      "_id": "6",
      "prompt": "Hello 6",
      "response": "Hi 6",
      "chatId": "6675ad0058154c87787cc4c4",
      "userId": "663a3f78970c6762815c0616')",
      "createdAt": "2024-06-22T14:56:01.653Z",
      "updatedAt": "2024-06-22T14:56:01.653Z"
    },
    {
      "_id": "7",
      "prompt": "Hello 7",
      "response": "Hi 7",
      "chatId": "6675ad0058154c87787cc4c4",
      "userId": "663a3f78970c6762815c0616')",
      "createdAt": "2024-06-22T14:54:01.899Z",
      "updatedAt": "2024-06-22T14:54:01.899Z"
    },
    {
      "_id": "8",
      "prompt": "Hello 8",
      "response": "Hi 8",
      "chatId": "6675ad0058154c87787cc4c4",
      "userId": "663a3f78970c6762815c0616')",
      "createdAt": "2024-06-22T14:53:20.837Z",
      "updatedAt": "2024-06-22T14:53:20.837Z"
    },
    {
      "_id": "9",
      "prompt": "Hello 9",
      "response": "Hi 9",
      "chatId": "6675ad0058154c87787cc4c4",
      "userId": "663a3f78970c6762815c0616')",
      "createdAt": "2024-06-22T14:11:52.343Z",
      "updatedAt": "2024-06-22T14:11:52.343Z"
    },
    {
      "_id": "10",
      "prompt": "Hello 10",
      "response": "Hi 10",
      "chatId": "6675ad0058154c87787cc4c4",
      "userId": "663a3f78970c6762815c0616')",
      "createdAt": "2024-06-22T14:08:03.669Z",
      "updatedAt": "2024-06-22T14:08:03.669Z"
    }
  ]
}
